Admission process. check.
Uniform. check.
School regulations. check.
Cockpit regulations. check.
Don't worry. Aerial.
I did an application for you. too.
Arriving at Front Sector 73.
Asticassia School of Technology. in five minutes.
The ship will now enter a docking course.
That's the school?
Mom. I finally made it!
What? No way! You can't!
This is the bridge.
-They'll die!
-What?
S-Someone is...
-Someone is outside!
-Rescue team. alert.
A person is in need of rescue.
-Prepare for extravehicular activity.
-Roger!
-Please confirm victim's status.
-It should be over here.
Are there any signs
of collision with debris?
If you move forward. you gain two.
What?
I'll save them!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
Leave the rescue to us!
Do they intend to leave the ship?
Damn it...
Attention mobile suit pilot!
We're opening the exit hatch.
Stay put until then!
I-I'm sorry.
If you spot someone
in need of rescue. let us know.
We'll respond immediately.
Yes sir!
Almost out of oxygen. Beginning rescue!
Are...
Are you okay?
Hello? Can you--
Don't interfere!
Excuse me?
I'd almost made my escape!
Because of you. it's all for nothing!
You'll take responsibility for this.
Sure.
Ms. Suletta Mercury?
Y-Yes!
You're here to observe the drills. right?
I'm Nika Nanaura.
a second-year student in Mechanics.
If you have any questions. just ask.
Yes. M...
Thank y...
-Thank y-you verr...
-Are you nervous?
I-I've never...
been to...
a school before.
It's your first time?
Say. is it true you're from Mercury?
Do people live there?
What's your major?
I'm in the Piloting department...
-That makes you one of the elite!
-What did you transfer here for?
My mother...
told me to go.
Your mother?
So did she also tell you
to wear that old-fashioned hair band?
Cut it out!
Yes. of course!
Seriously?
Miorine Rembran.
I've heard what happened.
Prepare immediately to join the class.
Yes sir.
I-I'll take...
I'll take responsibility!
I-I'll help you with your escape!
-Just tell me what I should do!
-It's you!
You're the girl who got in my way!
-Responsibility?
-What's that?
Idiot!
-This isn't the place...
-Responsibility. huh?
Why not let her take it?
You want to run away. right?
-To Earth.
-Class is in session!
No more chatter!
Earth?
A red Dilanza.
It must be Guel Jeturk.
Apologies for interrupting your drills.
This is an official duel.
approved by the Dueling Committee.
I. Shaddiq Zenelli. will be the witness.
I ask that no one interfere.
A duel?
Hey! That way is...
-No way.
-Are they coming toward us?
Go. Guel!
Get him!
Ms. Suletta!
You fool! Do you want to get hit?
Run!
Did you see that. Miorine?
How Guel Jeturk fights his duels!
Both you and the company
will be mine before long.
Class is still in session. brother.
Leave here immediately.
The bastard down there laughed at me.
Calling me a man with a runaway bride.
Bride?
That jerk.
Hold it. Miorine!
The rules say that when you lose.
you apologize like a groveling worm.
I want you to see how he does that.
I'm home.
E-Excuse me!
You again?
I-I just wanted to thank you
for saving me earlier.
M-Ms. Miorine.
-About your fiance--
-Stop. I never agreed to any of that.
You mean that guy
just decided on his own that you're engaged?
-It was a duel.
-What?
At our school.
the students settle
important matters through duels.
Money. authority. apologies...
Even marriage partners.
So you're going to marry him?
Why?
My lousy father designed it that way.
Jeturk Heavy Machinery.
Peil Technologies.
Grassley Defense Systems...
These three are the Benerit Group's
highest earners for this period.
However.
the Parneo Company has recorded a loss
for three consecutive periods.
Our group has no need
for companies in the red.
I am hereby suspending their access
to the group's finances.
Wait a minute. President Delling!
-If that happens. we'll go bank--
-Exactly.
You'll go bankrupt.
Their financial documents indicate
there is potential for recovery.
They've had their chance.
The only thing I'm interested in is results.
I've assigned two agents
to keep watch on Mistress Miorine.
Would you like to meet them?
For what?
You know better than to waste my time.
Stay out!
I-I'm sorry!
What is your deal?
Excuse me. what is that?
What is what?
It's a tomato. naturally.
That's a tomato?
What exactly do you Mercurians eat?
We do have tomato flavoring. but...
Here.
Th-Thank you!
Just bite into it.
It's good!
Not all tomatoes taste good.
That one's special.
My mother made it.
-She made a tomato?
-That specific breed. of course!
Your mother...
It's the same for me.
My mother
sent me here to study. so that I could
make Mercury a more prosperous planet.
That's why...
I see.
So your mother is still alive.
S-S-Sorry!
Hand me your student notebook.
Why?
You don't know the way back. right?
Once I've given you the school map app.
scram and leave me alone.
Playing farmer again?
All this pretending you're on Earth...
what's it good for?
Guel.
You can't just barge in here.
I came up with a bright idea.
From now on. you're gonna live
with us at Jeturk House.
We can't have any more
escape attempts. after all.
I never agreed to this.
It's your father who made the rules.
Do we always have to follow
what our parents decide?
Aren't you daddy's little lap dog.
What are you doing? Leave them alone!
Oh. how clumsy. my lady!
Better watch yourself!
W-We have to... we have to stop--
If you want to stop my brother. do it yourself.
Sh-She needs h...
I've been too lenient with you. it seems.
As your future husband.
I'll have to teach you some discipline.
You just need to shut your mouth
and give yourself over to me.
D-D-Didn't your mother ever teach you?
You can't act like that!
What the hell's your problem?
Don't you know who I am?
Um. well...
A pushy suitor?
I happen to be
the heir to one of
the three branches of the Benerit Group.
the head of the Dueling Committee.
and the reigning Holder!
Holder?
The school's number one pilot.
as chosen through duels.
Th-That may be true. but...
But what's wrong is wrong!
Please tell Ms. Miorine
that you're sorry!
Here at this school.
right and wrong are decided through duels.
Or would you like to duel me yourself?
I accept.
What?
You and I will duel!
Stop it! This has nothing to do with you!
Sounds fun.
If you lose. you'll have to leave the school.
-Right.
-You idiot!
I'll do it.
Send the carrier to Gate No. 2!
Load it with spare packs. too!
The carrier is now moving to Gate No.2.
Spare packages are loaded.
There's gonna be a duel!
With Mr. Guel!
-Who's he against?
-A transfer student. I hear.
Passage to tactical testing sector.
No obstacles.
Takeoff granted!
Are you sure about this?
If Delling dies.
my son Guel's engagement will be secured.
I have to act before the results
of these silly "duels" are nullified.
Set the detonation
for ten minutes after launch.
Delling...
our long friendship ends today.
Environmental setting data
for tactical testing sector received.
Coriolis correction. stable.
Bioinfo. identification complete.
Permet link. satisfactory.
KP001. Guel Jeturk.
Dilanza. let's go!
Show-off.
Aren't you going to watch. Elan?
Who cares.
Why accept a duel
from that country bumpkin?
I'll make it quick for her.
I'm the future ace of Dominicus. after all.
There she is. The Mercurian girl.
-Tricolor means a three-colored flag.
-She's got a flashy one. too.
-especially the national emblem of old France.
-I don't see a logo. Could it be handmade?
-Arriving at the designated coordinates.
-With mutual consent by both parties.
we will now begin the duel.
As always. victory will go
to the first one to break the blade antenna
of their opponent's mobile suit.
Both parties. face off!
-What?
-Isn't that the princess?
I thought it was the transfer student?
How did Ms. Miorine board Aerial?
Right.
Ms. Suletta?
What's wrong?
What's the meaning of this. Miorine?
I'm sick of people making decisions for me.
This is my fight!
Impudent girl. Have it your way.
I'll show you firsthand
that you're no match for me.
Guel?
Do you approve the change in duel opponent?
I approve.
Victory is never decided by
mobile suit performance alone.
Nor by the skill of the pilot. alone.
-The result itself is the only truth!
Fix release!
Weapons. Where are the weapons?
Did you think any amateur
could handle a mobile suit?
Two minutes left.
It's my life...
let me do as I please!
I'll decide for myself!
The princess of Management Strategy
has no chance of winning.
Take a good look at yourself.
You're nothing more than a trophy.
An alert?
What? An intruder?
Who the hell are you?
Exceeding speed limit.
Please decrease speed.
Why is it showing your name. Nika?
I guess I helped.
Why is--
What are you doing?
-Give it back!
-What?
Aerial is mine!
I told you. this has nothing to do with you!
Then fight in your own mobile suit!
-Don't be so stingy!
-What's going on?
-It's just another mobile suit!
-A falling-out?
Aerial isn't just another one!
We were raised together.
as family!
Family?
Why don't you let me fulfill
my responsibility by winning?
Aerial and I will never
lose to the likes of him!
"The likes of him"?
Shaddiq. I'm changing opponents again!
Give him the go ahead. Cecilia.
Sure thing.
Brother!
I'll correct your ignorance.
you country bumpkin!
Straight ahead!
My mother taught me.
"If you run. you gain one."
"but if you move forward. you gain two."
What?
When you run. you gain one by not losing.
But if you move forward...
You can win?
Whether you win or not.
there are two things you gain.
Experience and pride.
Not to mention trust!
A shield?
She blocked it.
In that case...
What just happened?
What kind of mobile suit is that?
GUND-ARM...
Gundam.
Wh-What... What the hell are you?!
It's time.
Mr. Jeturk.
-A last-minute intervention?
-No.
Your son was defeated in a duel.
What?
Even if you killed President Delling now.
Master Guel won't be Mistress Miorine's fiance.
Who was the opponent? Grassley?
-Peil?
-No.
It was...
Excuse me...
I-I won.
So it seems.
Suletta Mercury...
Huh? What the...
How did you...
This attire is the emblem of victory.
The emblem of the Holder.
It's also the emblem of my fiance.
I told you. didn't I? Those are the rules.
But I...
I'm a woman.
I guess Mercury is rather conservative.
That sort of thing is commonplace here.
Nice to meet you. my groom.
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam: The Witch from Mercury.
"The Cursed Mobile Suit."